hey what's up in this video I want to
talk about how to create an irresistible
offer that sells out in your business if
you are a coach course creator or
consultant and you're not getting the
kind of sales that you want this will
help you do that again for those of you
that I haven't met yet my name is jeremi
Kowski and for the last 21 years I have
built and scaled multiple coaching and
course businesses to over $20 million a
year and currently we are building a
business that is a seven figure business
in this space we help coach and course
creators make their first $10 to
$225,000 consistently a month I'm
talking about consistent recurring
Revenue in their business as coaches and
course graders and I want to talk to you
about creating that irresistible offer
that's going to do that for you now
without irresistable offer you're not
going to be able to get the kind of
clients that you want in your business
you need to be able to demonstrate to
people and show them that you understand
where they are coming from so that's one
of the first things that you need to
know is what is the pain points that
people have
and we're not talking about leading with
pain but we're talking about leading
people to their desire the way that we
create an irresistable offer is based on
what somebody desires everybody that we
meet has a desire and you can sell to
their desire when you know what it is
when we talk about our Niche that's a
type of person a specific psychographic
psychologically a way that a person
thinks that causes them to be drawn or
driven towards the thing that we help
them with so we can understand who we
help and what they desire now we craft
an offer around that I think a lot of
coaches and course creators get this
wrong and they actually think about okay
well what can I do and it comes from a
place of validation it comes from a
place of trying to prove themselves to
people and unfortunately that is a
recipe for failure anytime that you're
trying to build a business and you're
coming from a place of trying to prove
that you are worth something to people
you're not going to make any money so
the only way the only way that you can
make money in a coaching business is to
know who do you help and what do they
desire the most and again maybe you're
like I haven't picked that yet if that's
the case go to my YouTube channel type
in finding your Niche and this will help
you be able to do that I have a ton of
training on finding your Niche and the
process of doing that what I want to
talk about now is once you have your
Niche picked because that's what this is
and and and you're not going to be able
to literally do anything if you don't
know what your Niche is who do you help
how do you help them how do you take
them from point A to point B what is the
desire that they have from there what we
want to do is we want to step into their
shoes and understand what it's like to
have a day in the life of that person a
day in the life of the person who you
are selling to and this is something
that again most coaches and course
creators don't look at because they're
so focused on their framework they're so
focused on what do they deliver what do
I teach people you got to Det yourself
from what you teach in order to make any
kind of money that sells out in your
business I'm going to say that again you
need to detach yourself from what you
teach if you're going to make any kind
of money in your business and here's why
that is and how that
works because what we teach and what we
coach on and what we're actually
delivering if you lead with that you
will not make any money and
unfortunately that is what most of the
people that I meet they got an accept
courses exceptional coaching they're
starting and they're they're very
concerned about let's deliver results to
people results is important it's
important to deliver on what you say
it's important to have integrity to do
the things that you say that you're
going to do the problem is that that
does not actually connect with the
person that you are making an offer to
so I want to break this down for you
what is the difference between just
simply delivering value and actually
making an irresistible offer and for
those of you that I haven't talked to
yet we have a program called the client
growth accelerator program where I work
with you personally to actually build
your offer with you on my website you
can go check that out we're enrolling
students at strategic increments where
you can work with us and we can come
into your business and work with you to
help you actually put together your
irresistible offer and I'd love to do
that with you in our accelerator program
when we open the doors that currently
there's a waiting list you can jump on
that waiting list check that out out and
try it out with us when we open it up
now in your offer you got to understand
this is that there's two places that
your prospect are coming from number one
they are on the island of
uncertainty okay so the island of
uncertainty is where people are coming
from and there are shark infested waters
that are going to get them to their goal
now you exist over on the goal and I
want to tell you this is that you have
to be a product of the thing that you
are offering you have to embody the
thing that you are offering to people
when you look at me I am embodying what
I am promising to you I've created
results I know how to take you there I
have helped thousands of people go from
zero not doing anything not working in
their business have no clue what they're
doing starting out and building and
scaling something that is profitable my
client Kim I love the fact that she was
able to make over $20,000 in her first
offer that we put out there in a down
real estate market that was struggling
to be able to sell a real estate offer
by knowing how to craft an irresistible
offer and what she was able to do was
this is to create a bridge from
uncertainty to the goal in her prospects
so the shark infested waters was a down
Market whatever it is whatever Market
you're in whatever offer you're making
there is going to to be struggles that
people have and you are the solution
that allows them to bypass all of those
struggles whatever you are selling is
the result and transformation and
outcome that somebody can expect to get
that allows them to bypass all of the
things that they fear and worry about
now that's a bold ask and this is what I
tell people that you need to be able to
do when you make an irresistible offer
you need to make a bold scary Auda ious
promise the reason why is this because
if you don't you won't make any money
and unfortunately most coaches and
course creators are playing it
safe they are playing it safe about well
I don't want to overpromise and underd
deliver the fact of the matter is this
is that most people that are out there
if you've been in the coaching space for
a while and and by the way this this is
definitely a matter of Integrity are not
delivering on what they promise they're
not delivering on what they say that
they are going to deliver on and so if
you can just deliver on what you say
that you're going to deliver on and you
actually do the thing that you say that
you're going to do it will build trust
with people people will trust you and
the number one thing that converts
interest just people being interested in
what you're doing to actually buying the
thing from you is building trust they
have to know who you are they have to
like you and then they build trust with
you and so that comes from the way that
you grab people's attention with an
offer is a bold scary audacious promise
let me give you an example of what this
looks like if I just said simply I'm
going to show you how to build a landing
page in your business so that you get
clients that is not bold scary or
audacious there's a million people that
are out there that do that but if I say
I'm going to give you a proven blueprint
to make seven figures in a business
going from zero now that's bold that's
scary that's audacious and I better be
able to deliver on that and by the way I
know that I am able to deliver on that
because it's exactly what happens with
our clients that are in our program this
is exactly what I've done in my career
and that is why I wake up every single
morning and make videos like this this
is why I love to help people get results
in their business so once you
understand what are the fears what are
the worries what are the doubts or the
insecurities what are the things that
keep them up at night what causes them
to have
anxiety and let me pause here as coaches
we're like I don't want to talk about
negativity I want to talk about
positivity great please do in fact what
actually delivers an irresistible offer
is talking about positivity but you
can't talk about positivity without
understanding the negative energy that
somebody is facing when they look at
what their goal is when somebody sees
their goal the only that they actually
see when you are not
there because you arrive as an expert
you arrive as a mentor you arrive as a
help as a guide as somebody that can
show them the way and the path that they
didn't know how to get there and this
breaks down into the exact framework of
Joseph Campbell's the hero's journey and
the hero's journey is a powerful
powerful framework I want to actually
pull this up for you so you can see this
the heroes Journey there's a there's a
graphic that I love to pull up on this
for the hero's journey that breaks down
what an offer in your business actually
looks
like when you meet somebody in your
business this is them with a little
walking stick right here they are the
hero in their own
life they are going on an adventure
there's a call to Adventure right here
where it says a supernatural Aid
they cross over into the threshold to
find a mentor that walks them through
the challenges and
temptations that create death and
rebirth and by the way that's a good
thing because it's a death of the old
self and a rebirth transformation into
the new
self and as coaches and mentors that's
exactly what we help people do and so
inside of our programs there are
challenges and temptations that stop
people from doing that because they are
afraid to go after the thing that's
going to transform their life they are
afraid to change their life in that way
and when you can create transformation
inside of somebody's life it changes the
game for
them here's the problem most people that
are living on planet Earth right now are
not going to trust that you can actually
do
that and that that's the part that we
got to address when it comes to creating
an irresistible offer is we have to be
able to tap into two very important
aspects the emotional brain and The
Logical brain these two things work in
tandem together and that's what creates
an irresistible offer what gets somebody
to buy from you is when you tap into
their emotions and their
feelings and then you also validate it
with logic and this is how human beings
make decisions to buy anything all the
time now have you ever seen an offer
where you're like this is just BS this
is not true this is not going to get me
that result and you just are like this
is this is there's nothing there well
here's the problem it's because we're
not addressing those fears we're not
addressing those doubts we're not
addressing those insecurities and we're
not
connecting with somebody by going from
emotion to logic and passing through
into the realm of getting them to
understand what we
know anytime as a coach or Mentor that
you are trying to play the role of
Defense trying to get people to believe
you and you're worried that they're not
going to trust you you've already lost
the
game and by the way that has nothing to
do with your track record the amount of
case studies you have the quality of
your video content the quality of your
landing page or website has everything
to do with how you show up when you make
the offer and the modality that you're
able to take somebody from where they
just meet you to build a
connection and then persuade them to buy
from
you have you ever watched a movie where
you feel something a film a TV show
maybe a novel where you felt
something this is the the same aspect of
building an irresistible offer is
storytelling so when we craft our
irresistible offer we want to get very
specific about a bold scary audacious
promise this is our headline this is our
extra extra read all about
it and then we tell a story of how we're
able to take them from uncertainty to
their
goal and by doing this we are able to
walk people through a path to see
clearly a vision of the journey that
they're going on to be able to see the
future in their mind before it actually
happens that they have a vision of where
they are going before it actually
manifests for them and this is one of
the most important aspects of actually
building trust with people when you
create an irresistible offer as you're
able to help them see what it is that
they are going to experience by Future
pacing by showing the future reality to
them in their present reality before
they buy from you you end up promising
this to them you end up showing them how
it works the framework of it you give
them a bird's ey view overview of what
that looks like and when you do this
effectively you're able to take somebody
from just interested to becoming a
client of yours inside of my client
growth accelerator program every single
week I work with my clients to walk them
through how do we do this what are the
words that we say what are the things
that we put together I'm able to give
them feedback their ads and their offers
and their landing pages and their
presentations you're able to show them
okay do this don't do this we just had a
two-day Mastermind this last week where
I actually worked for two days with our
clients in a mastermind setting to be
able to put together what it's going to
take for them to break past their
limitations to be able to actually reach
the clients that they want and listen
I'd love to work with you inside of my
accelerator program if you're watching
this video I believe that that is
something that we should be doing
together I'd love to be able to show you
what it's like to be able to do that
again be sure to get on the waiting list
for my program sometimes we offer
different trial periods where you can
work with us inside of there and I'd
love to see you inside of my accelerator
program right now we have a free
training that we have actually put out
you can find the link below all about
how to get more clients with your
Facebook ads I'm showing you how we're
using Facebook ads to be able to get the
clients that you want in your business
we use Facebook ads to actually find the
people that we're looking for and so the
best way to actually connect with a
prospect with your IR irresistible offer
is to find somebody who's out there on
social media and pull them into some
kind of a presentation and the way that
we do this is we
leverage a lead magnet to be able to
deliver a high value freeb offer that
then builds trust with people that then
we can nurture that into a deeper
relationship with them so the way that
this works to actually build an
irresistible offer and how do you
actually take somebody from uncertainty
to that goal is you demonstrate it to
them and we do this in the form of
content we do this in the form of
various pieces of content that we can
put out there whether it be our social
media content we might make some YouTube
videos I might have a lead magnet with a
presentation on video of some kind a
training I might send some emails out to
people and when we utilize all of these
different
modalities we are able to build trust
through a sequence of events that allows
us to show somebody what it's going to
take for them to go from uncertainty
where they're at to the certainty that
they're looking for now it doesn't
happen overnight it doesn't happen in
one offer it doesn't happen in One
landing page it happens over a series of
touch points and connections that we
make with people
and so what we want to do is this is we
want to look at okay what is that bold
scary audacious promise that we're
making and then we want to look at what
is our framework that we coach people on
and we pull one piece from that
framework and that becomes our first
initial offer that we make when we're
creating a lead magnet when we're
getting people onto our email list this
creates lead flow of people that we're
able to connect with the way that you
sell to people is by creating an inbound
group of people that are looking for the
problem that you solve without having an
inbound group of people whether it comes
through organic social media content
paid social media people on your email
list you're not going to be able to grow
your business and most of the coaches
and course creators that I meet they're
trying to just put value out there
they're trying to put social media
content out there and get clients and
unfortunately that alone does not work
so you have to have some kind of an
anchored offer that you're able to draw
them into for instance I have this free
training that I put together all about
Facebook ads that is an anchored offer a
direct offer of a promise that I'm able
to deliver I'm going to show you in a
training how to build your ads what to
say what to Target and how to do that
now my coaching program is a much bigger
picture and piece of that but the
advertising piece is a way it's a door
into my world where somebody is able to
engage with me by coming into that
individual door and so that when I'm
able to pull people into that individual
door I'm able to build trust with them
I'm able to show them what it's like to
work with me they get on my email list
and that relationship continues and so
we've been able to close clients and get
more deals done by doing that now again
not one offer is going to create clients
for you this is where the nurture comes
in this is why we create additional
pieces of content one piece of content
doesn't make your business it's about a
lifestyle of becoming a content
creator and if you are a coach or a
course creator the way that you actually
grow your business is you create a
lifestyle of being a content creator
somebody that knows what to say in your
content that gets people to take action
how do you build trust with people in
your content how do you walk them
through that how do we bring and then
what do you do that's different on a 30
second Instagram reel or a 30 minute
YouTube video or a hourlong video
presentation that you might be doing
what do you say that's different that
actually builds that trust when you can
do this when you make a bold scary
audacious promise you're able to pull
people into your world onto an email
list and then you're able to create
content in the form of video that you
send to people this builds trust because
they're able to watch you they're able
to hear your voice they're able to see
what it's like to work with you and by
the way listen you don't have to be as
articulate as I am I've been doing this
for a long time when I started I sucked
at making video it's terrible didn't
know how to do it didn't know how to
talk didn't know how to communicate and
now comes very naturally to me I'll tell
you though even every time I make a
video even before this video right here
I had a I had some nerves I was like
what do I say how am I going to say it
and I sat down and I used one of my
favorite tools that actually gives us
ideas to come up with our videos what I
did was I went over to artificial
intelligence and and I'm not reading a
script from AI or anything but I was
able to use the AI to give me ideas of
what to talk about in this video in fact
I want to pull some of those up for you
where you can actually see this I'm
going to actually pull the curtain back
on this right now in my office and I'm
going to show you what this looks like
for
you I have a document right here that we
actually had AI generate that talks
about the things that I want to talk
about here now where did it come up with
this content well it came up with this
based on conversations that I actually
had with my coaching clients and this is
one of the really cool things that you
can do is that once you have a
connection with your coaching clients
you're able to take the recordings of
that and the transcripts and we have
transcripts in a tool called
otter.ai I have transcripts of every
single session of coaching training and
everything that I've ever done and what
I'll do is I'll actually pull some of
these in here like here's a podcast
episode that we did right here here's
the transcript of it I'm able to pull
the transcripts of the sessions that I'm
doing into Ai and I'm able to have it
come up with ideas for me I want to show
you how just how quickly and easily this
is to do if I just take this one
transcript here of a podcast that I did
or let's say it was a coaching session
or something like that I can go into Ai
and I can say this to give me ideas map
out 20 ideas for Unique YouTube videos
that are relevant to the people who
would listen to the podcast transcript
below make it different topics than the
actual podcast but ideas that will
connect with the type of person who
would be a listener and I feed a lot of
my content into AI with this one prompt
right here and then I'll paste the
transcript and then we'll see what it
gives us right here here's 20 ideas
right here mastering your morning
routine productivity hacks I probably
should make that top five mistakes
entrepreneur would make how to balance
Family Life creating irresistible lead
magnets behind the scenes of a sixf
figure business launch psychology of
selling again these are all really great
mastering Evergreen funnels I was going
to make one like that for this as well
mindset shifts to overcome income
plateaus and by the way we have a lot of
YouTube videos on this channel where you
can check that out a lot of different
topics where we've talked about on how
to do this but that's one of the ways
that we come up with ideas to be able to
actually create that for us let's say
that I was going to create a training on
this topic right here map out an outline
for a YouTube video
that is 1 hour long and I don't make it
an hour long but let's just try this I
use that as a prompt even though I'm
only going to maybe make it 30 minutes
long I'm going to say an hour long based
on this for the for the person above
okay and so it's going to start to map
out for me an outline for a video piece
of content that I could create now
obviously these are tools that I don't
even use things like that maybe I could
feed into it what are the tools that we
actually use they can give me stuff like
that but this gives you an idea of how
to come up with content ideas without
having to be a Super Genius that has all
of these ideas in your head all the time
but I'll tell you this once you work
with enough clients once you work with
people once you connect with people your
key your goal your mission is to connect
with people that you can work
with they will tell you what they want
to learn from you your interactions with
real people will actually tell you that
if you're wondering how do I know what
their desires are how do I know what
their goals are how do I know where
they're struggling or what they want to
accomplish how do I know what their land
of uncertainty is and where they want to
get to and how to bridge that Gap it's
when you start connecting with people
that have those problems now ai can help
us brainstorm some of those ideas to
start to attract that audience to us but
the real magic happens when we actually
start to engage with people we start
building lead magnets we start growing
our email list and we start talking to
real people about how to grow their
business now if you're a coach if you're
a course creator and you want to know
how do we do this inside of my
accelerator program every single week we
work with people to be able to put this
together and I and I I actually put this
uh a graphic on the screen here I want
you to check out that this is exactly
what we do every single week inside of
my program is we help you know how to
find your
Niche how to write your sales copy how
to optimize your content ads and funnels
and how to master sales skills that sell
so that you have consistent cash flow
massive impact and persuasive messaging
and this is the Triad that creates
financial and time freedom in your life
and so if you want to work with somebody
that can show you how to do that if you
want to know how to optimize your ads
and funnels and and write sales copy
that converts and then master the skills
of sales in your business stay connected
with us plug in subscribe to the channel
join us on one of our free trainings you
can find in the description below get on
the waiting list for our accelerator
program and continue to follow what
we're doing what we're teaching I'd love
to work with you I'd love to continue
this conversation and this journey
together stay plugged in I'll see you on
the next video we'll talk soon